[BEA] Ma, why are there only three plates?
Is Papa not coming home?
Isn't he joining us?
[MARIELA]
You really take after your father.
You're both useless!
Are you going to take his side? Huh?
Then get out of here and go with him!
You deserve each other anyway!
- [MARIELA SCREAMING]
- [PLATES SHATTERING]
Ma.
Don't tell them
that you know
they're Papa's second family.
Why not?
[BEA] That's a strong motive.
It'll just prove that you're going after
Papa's illegitimate child.
We'll get into more trouble.
[ENRICO] I don't know if Billy will ever
be able to forgive me
for what I'm about to tell her.
But she needs to know the truth.
You know, I've always wondered,
"What if you'd been there
the night Oliver was born?"
"Would Mama still be alive?"
Because I knew that if you were there,
you wouldn't abandon us.
I'm sorry.
[SOBBING]
I hope you can all forgive me.
Billy, are you sure you're ready?
We don't really have a choice.
LoveList can't afford to slow down now.
Jumping in on the budget discussion,
I'll also present the projected cost
for our new security upgrades.
How bad are the numbers?
They are pretty high, chief.
Then we really don't have a choice.
We need to close this deal
with Claire Fabrizio.
Okay?
- [PHONE CHIMES]
- [ROWENA] Ralph! Son.
[CHUCKLES] My son.
Say hi to your aunties.
- Ah…
- My son, Ralph.
Hello.
I heard the news.
The drama of that company, it never ends.
Ma, please. Come on.
I told you, it's a mess there.
That company is bound to fail
sooner or later.
Get out while you still can.
Okay.
You know I just want
what's best for you, son.
What's best for me?
What's best for me
is for you to stop controlling
all my decisions.
Wow.
You don't get it, do you?
I'm doing all this for your sake.
For your future.
Ma.
I spoke with the lawyer.
She said it's possible
you'll be moved to a hospital.
Isn't that great, Ma?
You won't rot here anymore.
You can get out.
Which hospital?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
The…
ward.
- She's crazy. She's going to a psych ward.
- [MARIELA] Wait, the psych ward?
- What am I, crazy?
- [LAUGHS] She admitted it.
You want to be away from me, right?
- [WOMAN] It came from her.
- Ma, no. You're not crazy.
Ma, just think about it.
You'll be better off there.
You'll be taken care of.
Turns out she really is crazy.
- [WOMEN CACKLING]
- She belongs there.
- Ma. Hey, Ma!
- Hey!
- Let go of me! Ouch!
- Stop it, Ma!
- [WOMAN] Stay out of this!
- [BEA] What the hell?!
- Stop it!
- Ma! Ma!
- [GRUNTS SOFTLY]
- Ma!
- Miss! Miss, help! Help!
- [WOMAN] Hey! Hey! Hey!
- Hey! What's going on there?!
- Hey! Here she comes!
[WOMAN] They started it! They're psychos!
Stop it! Quiet down!
My mother needs a doctor!
Miss, call a doctor!
My mother needs one now!
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Boss.
[OVERLAPPING, INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- Is this tequila?
- Uh, yes.
[YANI] We're starting early.
Speaking of which, let's do a shot.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES]
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
- [FRIENDS GUSHING]
[RALPH] Okay. Perfect, perfect.
Just right, just right.
Okay, cheers
to our second anniversary, babe.
- Come on.
- Cheers.
- Cheers!
Happy second anniversary!
- Cheers, everyone!
- Cheers, guys!
- Oh, yes.
- Cheers!
Mm-hmm.
Ah!
[RALPH] There you go.
- [YANI] Whoo!
- [RALPH] That's so good. Mmm!
[YANI] Oh!
- [RALPH] Is it okay?
- [YANI] Uh-huh!
- [GLASSES CLINKING]
- [TONI] You want more?
What? Still working?
I have to.
Thanks for the treat!
[YANI] Oh, right.
Toni said it was just going to be
you two celebrating.
What happened?
Uh, well…
We wanted to celebrate with you guys.
I mean, come on, it's more fun
to celebrate with friends, right?
- Right.
- Yeah?
- [TONI] Is that so?
- [YANI] Okay.
Well then, cheers to the couple!
- Cheers!
- Cheers, guys.
- Okay.
- Cheers!
- Cheers, guys!
- To justice!
- Yes!
- To justice.
- [CHUCKLES]
Good thing those menaces are
behind bars now, chief.
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
[BLAIRE] Huh?
Billy.
- Yes?
- Guys.
This is about Charm and Ralph.
Let's stop stressing out.
Right?
Here. Dude.
- [YANI] This one's good.
- [CLINKS]
[TONI] Wait, it is.
- [YANI] So good!
- [BLAIRE] I think it's shrimp.
- This one too!
- [BLAIRE] It's so fresh!
It's just a minor cut.
Huh? A minor cut?
Doc, my mother hit her head pretty hard.
You're saying it's just a minor cut?
She should be transferred to a hospital!
Nurse, call on the guards.
They may be taken back to their cells.
Ah-- Doc!
[SIGHS] She should be at the hospital.
[SIGHS]
Let's go, Ma.
- [GRUNTS AGGRESSIVELY]
- Rest up--
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What's wrong?
You want me to get sent
to the mental hospital.
You want to get rid of me!
Ma, that's not it!
I don't want to see you
in such a sorry state.
I can't stand seeing you suffer.
That's why you should be transferred
to a hospital. A general hospital.
If I get transferred to a hospital,
you won't be there.
That's why I don't want to!
I don't want to!
- [SHUSHING] Ma, calm down.
- I don't want to!
- Okay, okay.
- I don't want to go there!
That's enough, Ma.
- Don't force me!
- Okay, I won't.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Bro, I'll be right back.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
VISTING AREA RULES
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What do you want?
Let me join your group.
I can help.
Promise.
What help are you talking about?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I know about your plan.
- On Family Day, right?
- [SUSPENSEFUL STING]
Keep your mouth shut.
Please, hear me out.
[CALOY] Listen.
Once you get out of here,
what'll you do?
Go into hiding for the rest of your life?
How is that any different
from being imprisoned?
I can help you.
I know someone.
He can give us new names
and a new life.
We can live as a different person
without anyone going after us.
[EXHALES]
But before that,
of course you need to let me in your group
and help me get out of here too.
So I can finally be with her.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Um, Billy?
Some of your stuff is still in my unit.
I'll just send it to you.
You know you can still stay there, right?
You just want to leave
as soon as possible.
No, it's all good. Thank you, Charm.
There's just too many of us.
My father is staying with us now too.
Thank you.
You're on good terms now?
He saved Oliver and Aunt Pres, so…
I owe him that.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
You won't regret your decision, Billy.
And I'm happy for you.
[CHARM] Because
you won't go through what I experienced.
Babe?
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
You know that
my mother is a single parent, right?
And I used to always make her feel that
what she was doing for me wasn't enough.
Because of that,
she felt she had to work abroad.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
But…
[INHALES SHARPLY]
…she had only been abroad for a few years…
when she got into an accident.
She died.
[CHARM BREATHES DEEPLY]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I blame it on myself because…
she wouldn't have left
if it weren't for me.
But do you know what hurts more than that?
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
She died while we were
still not on good terms.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I wasn't able to ask for her forgiveness.
[CHARM SNIFFLES]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[CHARM] Before,
I wanted you to stand your ground.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I always told you that I hoped…
you'd learn how to fight.
But now that it has come to this…
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm reminded of how I didn't
obey my mother back then.
[CHARM] So if I were you, babe…
Be with your mom.
Do something to make amends with her.
Babe.
You know what she wants, right?
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOFT SOB] If we need to…
break up for now, it's okay.
I'll be fine.
Just fix your relationship
with your mom first.
[CHARM] Just look at Billy.
She chose to forgive.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Billy…
Can you… can you, like, honestly say
that, you know, things are getting better?
You know, I didn't want to meddle, but
Charm has a point.
[BILLY] Our parents
won't be with us forever.
So while you still have time,
talk to her.
Talk to your mom.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Wow.
It's like you're a different
person already.
You know how to forgive now.
For your brother.
For Auntie Pres.
And for myself.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[JORDAN HUMMING]
♪ I got lost again ♪
♪ Like I learned nothing before ♪
♪ How many thousands of roads ♪
♪ Will I walk before giving up ♪
♪ Just to find you
And for you to find me? ♪
♪ I hope your heart can save me ♪
♪ If there are challenges ♪
♪ Save this feeling and help me ♪
♪ My muse ♪
♪ Where's our destination? ♪
♪ You are the captain ♪
♪ I'll follow wherever you go ♪
♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ I'll ride your wave ♪
♪ Wherever it takes me ♪
♪ Do you know when I found you ♪
♪ Everything changed? ♪
♪ Wherever I go ♪
♪ My heart won't be lost ♪
♪ Even if you let go, I'll come back ♪
♪ Do you know when I found you ♪
♪ Everything changed? ♪
♪ Wherever I go ♪
♪ I'm coming home ♪
♪ I'm already weak and wounded ♪
♪ It seems I'm drowning in sorrow ♪
♪ I let everything go ♪
FIRE BURNS DOWN HOME
♪ The pain has reached my throat ♪
♪ My muse ♪
♪ Where's our destination? ♪
♪ You are the captain ♪
♪ I'll follow wherever you go ♪
♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ I'll ride your wave ♪
♪ Wherever it takes me ♪
♪ Do you know when I found you ♪
♪ Everything changed? ♪
♪ Wherever I go ♪
♪ My heart won't be lost ♪
♪ Even if you let go, I'll come back ♪
♪ Do you know when I found you
Everything changed? ♪
♪ Stay right there, my love ♪
♪ Because I'm coming home ♪
♪ Oh my God, I'm so in love ♪
♪ From then until now ♪
[JORDAN] Your turn!
♪ Oh my God, I'm so in love ♪
♪ So in love ♪
[JORDAN] Yes! One more time!
♪ Oh my God, I'm so in love ♪
♪ From then until now ♪
♪ I'm coming home ♪
- [APPLAUSE]
- [JORDAN] Thank you!
[AUDIENCE CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
[JORDAN] Make some noise
for Sir Luke April!
[AUDIENCE CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
The CCTV technician will come tomorrow.
Yup, at 2:00 p.m.
I'll arrive at one.
- Okay.
- Me too, boss.
- Yes. Thank you.
- Okay.
- [RAIN] Bye, boss.
- [ROBBIE] Don't forget to lock the door.
Dude.
I thought you went home.
Um, I just wanted to ask something.
What is it?
Are we okay?
Yeah. What do you mean?
There's something you're not telling me.
Jordan, say it. Come on.
What is it?
[LAUGHS]
Is it that obvious?
Jordan, please.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Right now?
Shit. Okay.
[EXHALES SHARPLY] I'll admit it.
Dude, I…
I'm in love with you.
["THE PUZZLE" BY BELLE MARIANO PLAYING]
I requested that, if possible,
she be transferred to a hospital.
[ATTORNEY] We have strict laws
when it comes to this.
You keep spouting all this stuff.
Tell your client that
I won't back down.
Does Billy know that
she has other siblings?
I don't know how to tell her.
I don't want to hurt her.
What happened to us
was devastating.
But when I found out
that Dad didn't forget about me,
everything we had lost
didn't seem to matter anymore.
Because Dad came back to us.
Precious. I have something
to tell you and Billy.
We need to find potential investors.
If not Claire, then who?
If not the US, then where?
- Let's regroup tomorrow morning.
- Tomorrow is Saturday.
Dude, sorry. Maybe we can
do a Zoom meeting?
The company is literally
bleeding right now.
Where is your commitment
to your work?
Is everything ready for Family Day?
I don't have all day.
I'm a busy person.
Billy, sorry.
Your apology won't erase
all the harm you've done to my family.